adjingo.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy - AdJingo.com

## Privacy Policy

**AdJingo Privacy Policy**

and benefit in search engine popularity, search engine optimization and getting additional links to your website. Trading relevant links with related websites helps with search engine relevance. Trade links with advertising related products or services. Create backlinks to your website, get more exposure in the search engines and more.  
Get more traffic, build more backlinks and more! 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

AdJingo collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. AdJingo collects information from users responding to ads regarding their Internet provider; this information may include the user's IP address, host name, country of origin and Internet provider being used. This collected information may be shared with the user placing the ad for the sole purpose of assisting this user in determining the validity and legitimacy of the response. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We may use information collected to promote other affiliate programs, products, web sites and services. 

Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by AdJingo and may be shared with third parties whose services are used for traffic analysis purposes. This information includes: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by AdJingo to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics. 

**COOKIES**  
A cookie is a small text file stored on the client user's hard drive containing information about the user. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, a cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie for AdJingo, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**LINKS**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that AdJingo.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Using Information from AdJingo.  
**You may use personal information gathered from AdJingo only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that. 

**DISCLOSURE**  
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Site. 

**General.** We may update this policy at any time 

April 2008
